[Music]
i always believe in taking risks and
succeeding
i like to work on my own terms and in my
own way i wasn't cut out for a 9-5 job i
went with my heart
my family has always supported me and
given me the freedom to do what i wanted
i created something successful
on my own apni dumper but today the
risks are quite high as compared to a
year back
things are pretty uncertain article
anything can happen to anyone anna
and it's not just the future of my
business
mary family b
their future worries me and now it's my
turn to support them
[Music]
i'm looking at securing their future
today and tomorrow
after all family comes first
[Music]
you